

Muhammad Awais Ajmal

Senior Unity Game Developer

awaisajmal02@gmail.com

Bahawalpur, Pakistan

+923039269518

0

linkedin.com/in/https://shorturl.at/AHM49

in

In my 3 years as a Unity game developer, I've mastered diverse genres, excelled in teamwork, honed my skills in gameplay, UI, performance, and monetization, and learned the importance of timely, high-quality delivery. Ready for more challenges ahead!

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sr. Game Developer

Five River Solution

11/2023 - Present

Islamabad,Pakistan

Game DeveloperFive River Solution

Tive raver solderon

09/2022 - 10/2023 Islamabad, Pakistan

Jr. Game Development

3 Ace Studio

01/2022 - 08/2022 Bahawalpur,punjab,Pakistan

Jr. Game Developer

JHU Technology

08/2021 - 12/2021 Bahawalpur, Punjab, Pakistan

Internship Unity Game Developer

JHU Technology

05/2021 - 07/2021 Bahawalpur, Punjab, Pakistan

EDUCATION

Master in Computer Science

The Islamia University of Bahawalpur

2020 - 2022 Bahawalpur Pakistan(3.81/4)

Bechelor in Computer Science

The Islamia University of Bahawalpur

2016 - 2020 Bahawalpur Pakistan (3.71/4)

Diploma of Associate Engineering(Civil)

TEVTA Punjab

2013 - 2016 Bahawalpur Pakistan (83.82%)

SKILLS

C# Un

Unity Game Development

Game Desigr

Problem Solving

Game Planing

PROJECTS

Offroad coach bus simulator

https://rb.gv/grv1g

Forest Wild Werewolf Hunting

- https://rb.gy/y61ea

House Makeover Cleaning

https://rb.gy/y7hsdu

Scary Grandma Grandpa House 3D

https://shorturl.at/Oi8dB

Angry My Neighbor

https://rb.gy/6f7e2a

Supermarket Simulator: Shop 3D

- https://shorturl.at/gtPKD ☑

Real World T20 Cricket 2024

https://shorturl.at/lNVQj

Car Driving School Games Sim

https://shorturl.at/6BFcB

STRENGTH

Good Communication Skills

Team Player

Time Management

LANGUAGES

English

Urdu

Professional Working Proficiency Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Research

Play Video Games

Education

Hiking